本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
你被监视着
You are being watched.
■
・ 翻译  阿好
・ 翻译  卫老哥
■
・ 翻译  茶炒栗子
・ 翻译  天朝直属
政府有一套秘密系统
The government has a secret system--
■
・ 翻译  王小麦
・ 翻译  艾瑞卡
一台每时每刻都在监控你的机器
a machine that spies on you every hour of every day.
■
翻  幸田实果子
译  灰灰是菇凉
我设计这台机器是为了侦测恐怖行动
I designed the machine to detect acts of terror
■
・ 校对  阿好
但它却看到了一切
but it sees everything--
■
压制  灰灰是菇凉
牵涉普通人的暴力罪行
violent crimes involving ordinary people.
阿包  凭陵新月  Sagelibra  兜兜兜爹  阿包  凭陵新月  Sagelibra  兜兜兜爹  阿包  凭陵新月  Sagelibra  兜兜兜爹  阿包  凭陵新月  Sagelibra  兜兜兜爹
■
时间轴
政府认为这些人无关紧要
The government considered these people irrelevant.
我们不
We don't.
受当局追捕  我们只能秘密活动
Hunted by the authorities, we work in secret.
你永远找不到我们
You'll never find us.
特效
灰灰
但无论是受害人还是行凶者
But victim or perpetrator,
总监
阿好
只要你的号码被列出来  我们就会找到你
if your number's up, we'll find you.
疑犯追踪
第三季 第十五集
纽约
-911报警电话  有什么紧急情况  -冷静下来
- 911. What is your emergency? - I need you to calm down.
911接入电话
分析911信号
妨害治安
暴力程度
-911报警电话  有什么紧急情况  -闭嘴  闭嘴
- 911. What's your emergency? - Shut up! Shut up!
入室行窃
暴力程度
家庭纠纷
911报警电话  有什么紧急情况
911. What's your emergency?
911报警电话
911.
911报警电话  有什么紧急情况
911. What's your emergency?
快救救我  他们闯进我车里了
You gotta help me. They've broken into my car.
您现在在车里吗  先生
Are you in the car now, sir?
没在  谢天谢地  我在街对面
No. Thank God. I'm across the street.
好的  请不要试图靠近车
Good. Please do not attempt to approach the vehicle.
您有看到武器吗
Now do you see any weapons?
他们在车里撒欢儿呢  到处都是
They're ripping up the interior. They're everywhere!
好吧  他们是想偷车吗
All right, and are they attempting to steal the vehicle?
什么  开什么玩笑
What? Don't be ridiculous.
松鼠又不会开车
Squirrels can't drive.
恐怕松鼠不归911报警电话管
I'm afraid squirrels fall outside the purview of 911.
我帮您转到非紧急线接线员
Let me connect you to a non-emergency operator.
干得好  哈罗德
Good job, Harold.
你确定以前没做过类似的工作吗
You sure you've never done this kind of thing before?
没怎么做过
Not quite,
但是有过  类似经验
although I do have some applicable experience.
我可不确定呢  芬奇
I don't know, Finch.
也许我们应该让弗斯科去审问下那些松鼠
Maybe we should get Fusco to question those squirrels.
里瑟说得是
Reese is right.
没准儿是个啮齿族偷车团伙
Could be a whole rodent carjacking ring.
别只顾着好玩  行么
Keeping entertained, are we?
我很乐意跟你易地而处  肖女士
I'd be happy to trade places, Ms. Shaw.
我都不明白  为什么说我最适合
I admit I'm not sure what makes me the best fit
本次卧底工作
for this particular undercover mission.
对着桌子  守着监控
At a desk, surrounded by monitors,
救人于危难之中
helping people in danger.
就差一条狗了
All you're missing is the dog.
再说了  你真希望有人打911求救
Besides, would you really want someone to call 911
被我接到电话吗
and get me?
言之有理
Point taken.
这些电话代表了我们没接到的号码
These calls represent the numbers we never get.
这些罪行是突发的  机器都没办法侦察到
Crimes that unfold too quickly for the machine to detect.
所以这是双赢啊  芬奇
So it's a win-win, Finch.
又能帮助他们  又能看住这位最新的号码
You get to help them while looking into our latest number.
桑德拉・尼克尔森
Sandra Nicholson.
911接线员兼见习主管
911 operator and trainee supervisor.
她颇有盛誉啊
She's got a stack of commendations.
专题聚焦: 桑德拉・尼克尔森
威胁何在
So what's the threat?
911接线员经常成为庭审证人
911 operators are often witnesses at trial,
起诉对象
targets of lawsuits,
以及
and...
我黑进了路由系统
now that I've hacked the routing system,
可以监控她接到的每一通电话
I can monitor every call she gets.
桑德拉
Sandra?
她开车坠桥落水了
Her car went off a bridge into the water.
正在下沉  我不知道该怎么办
She's sinking. I don't know what to do.
好的  女士  您能听到我吗  您叫什么名字
Okay, hello, ma'am, can you hear me? What's your name?
杰姬  我被困住了  我的天啊
Jackie. I'm trapped. Oh, my God.
好了  杰姬  放松
All right, Jackie, just relax.
我们会帮你脱身的  好吗
We're gonna get you outta there. Okay?
汽车能在水面漂浮两分钟
Cars can float for up to two minutes,
我们还有点时间
so we got a little time.
门卡住了  车窗也短路了
The doors are stuck, and the windows have shorted out.
-救命  -杰姬  你穿高跟鞋了吗
- Please help. - Jackie, are you wearing heels?
是  倒霉的十厘米高跟
Yes, these stupid 4-inch pumps.
好了  高跟可以救你一命了
All right, those pumps are gonna save your life.
车窗户最薄弱的地方在前边靠门铰处
Your car window's weak spot is up front near the door hinges.
用你的高跟鞋拼命砸那里
I want you to kick that spot as hard as you can with your heel,
明白吗  动手
okay? Go!
成功了
It worked!
1234队到达现场
Unit 1234 arriving on scene.
我们看到车了  交给我们
We have eyes on the car. We'll take it from here.
好了  杰姬  救援队这就到了
All right, Jackie. Rescue team's on the way.
她很棒
She's good.
处理别人的紧急情况很棒
At handling other people's emergencies.
临到自己了就不知道怎么样了
Wonder how she'll hold up when she's faced with one of her own.
吉卜林一案的凶器
Murder weapon on the Kipling case.
你怎么看  弗斯科  尺寸正确  形状正确
What do you think, Fusco? Right size, right shape?
刀刃错误
Wrong edge.
伤口是锯齿状的  记得不
Wound was serrated, remember?
弗斯科  等等
Fusco, hold up a second.
那嫌犯妥妥有罪
Suspect's guilty as hell,
但是没有搜查令我们拿不到他的DNA
But we can't get his DNA without a warrant.
地检官要放了他
The D.A. wants to kick him.
听说过"垃圾搜寻"没  凯恩
Ever hear of dumpster diving, Kane?
打扰一下  弗斯科警探
Excuse me. Detective Fusco?
杰克・哈里森
Jake Harrison.
刚从十二分局调过来的
Just transferred over from the 12th,
我在查这案子
and I caught this case.
塔拉・库克  二十九岁
Tara Cooke, 29.
昨天上午在东河边被发现的
Found by the east river yesterday morning.
头部受击  钱包被偷
Head bashed in, wallet stolen.
是抢劫失手  对吧
Mugging gone bad, right?
大家都说应该向你请教
Everyone said you were the guy to talk to.
听着  小子
Look, kid,
人家不会凭空就把你调来凶案组
they bumped you up to homicide task force for a reason.
别什么事儿都等人家指示
They don't all come with instructions.
自己想去
Figure it out.
你也想找我帮忙
You want something from me too?
不是时候吗  警探
Is this a bad time, detective?
不是好时候
It ain't good.
我脑子里一堆事儿
My brain's being picked on everything
什么审讯犯人  什么证据收集
from interrogation to evidence collection.
意料之中
Hardly surprising.
逮捕西蒙斯警员
Your arrest of Officer Simmons
令你声名鹊起  备受敬重
brought you no small amount of esteem.
你应该感到荣幸啊
Perhaps you should be flattered
你的同僚都来向你求助
that your peers are soliciting your advice.
是啊  是啊
Yeah, yeah.
说到这个  你收到我发给你的名字了吗
Speaking of which, did you receive the name I sent?
收到了  是
Yeah, it was, uh...
桑德拉・尼克尔森
Sandra Nicholson.
除了几张停车罚单以外
Yeah, I mean, other than a couple of parking tickets,
她没有任何案底
she's clean.
但她有一个封存的少年犯罪记录
But she did have a sealed juvie record.
一定是小时候惹过什么事
Must have gotten into some kind of trouble as a kid.
我想你应该没办法查看
I don't suppose you could take a peek
封存的记录吧
behind that seal.
抱歉了  兄弟
I'm sorry, pal.
HR这事儿闹的  警方深受影响
With the whole HR takedown, hit the force pretty hard.
整个警局被盯得死死的
The whole department's under scrutiny.
除非有法院传票
So unless you got a court order,
否则我也没办法
I guess I'm gonna have to say no.
理解  感谢帮助  警探
Understood. I thank you for your time, Detective.
至于目前的超强人气嘛  你名至实归
And as for your newfound popularity, you've earned it.
好吧
Yeah.
看到这些淤青没
See these bruises?
尸斑
Livor mortis.
尸体长时间受压的地方才会出现  知道吗
Happens when a body stays in one place, okay?
塔拉被发现时是右侧着地
Tara was found on her right side.
而这些淤青是在左边
These bruises are on the left.
看这儿
And look.
法医鉴定发现伤口有工业地毯纤维
Forensics found industrial carpet fibers stuck in the wound.
但她并没有被地毯包裹着
But she wasn't wrapped up in any carpet.
尸体被移动过
Body was moved.
这根本不是抢劫
This isn't a mugging at all.
开始调查吧  说说还有什么发现
Let's get to work. Show me what else you got.
好
Yeah.
电话打进
911报警电话  有什么紧急情况
911. What's your emergency?
我叫亚伦
My name is Aaron.
有人要闯进我家
Some men are trying to break into my apartment.
亚伦  我叫桑德拉
Aaron. I'm Sandra.
我会帮你  好吗  你是一个人吗
I'm gonna help you out, okay? Are you alone?
我从学校回家时保姆不在
The sitter wasn't here when I got home from school,
我妈妈在上班
and mom's at work.
好的  马上安排警察赶过去
All right, I'm sending the police right away.
全体注意  贝克斯菲尔德216号4E非法入室
All units, 1031 in progress. 216 Bakersfield way, unit 4E.
情况紧急  重复  情况紧急
Code three. Repeat, code three.
里瑟先生  肖女士  他虽然不是我们的号码  但
Mr. Reese, Ms. Shaw, he may not be our number, but...
明白  芬奇  马上去
We got it, Finch. We're on our way.
桑德拉  他们要破门而入了
Sandra, they're breaking through the door.
有没有地方可以躲
Is there any place you can hide?
我衣橱板后面有个空隙
There's a crawlspace behind a panel in my closet.
很好  快去
Perfect. Go there now.
好了  桑德拉  我在里面了
Okay, Sandra, I'm in.
好  你做得很好  亚伦
Okay, you're doing great, Aaron.
现在你要保持绝对安静  别出声
Now I want you to stay super quiet, not a sound.
桑德拉
Sandra?
成功了  他们走了
It worked. They're leaving.
电量过低
不要
No!
亚伦
Aaron?
不不不不
No, no, no! No!
亚伦  你还好吗
Aaron, are you all right?
-亚伦  -不
- Aaron! - No!
桑德拉
Sandra?
这些人有话要我转告你
The men want me to tell you something.
什么话
What--what is it?
接你的手机
Answer your phone.
什么
What?
电话打进
未知号码
喂
Hello?
很高兴认识你  桑德拉
So nice to meet you, Sandra.
很抱歉给你的私人手机打电话
I apologize for calling you on your personal cell phone,
但是我们接下来要一起做的事
but for what we're about to do together,
需要你可以移动
I need you mobile.
我们要做什么
And what are we about to do?
我要你做什么你就做什么
Anything I say.
这个小男孩是我的人质
You see, I've just taken this boy hostage,
你要一字不差地听从我的指示
and unless you follow my instructions precisely,
不然小亚伦就要送命了
little Aaron is going to die.
你是谁  你叫什么
Who is this? What's your name?
真的吗  桑德拉
Really, Sandra?
孩子命在旦夕
A boy's life is at stake,
你还想先自我介绍啊
and you want proper introductions.
我怎么知道这个亚伦是真的
How do I know Aaron is even real...
这个绑架不是假的
that this kidnapping wasn't staged?
我很乐意把亚伦的手砍下来
I'd be happy to cut off Aaron's hand
扔在你位于17大道3621室的公寓外面
and dump it outside your apartment at 3621 17th Avenue.
看看你的手机
Take a look at your phone.
图片信息发送自
未知号码
告诉我  你想让我先砍他哪一部分
Now tell me exactly which body part you'd like him to lose first.
不
No!
-我相信你  -很好
- I believe you. - Good.
基本规则
Now for the ground rules.
敢通知任何人  违背任何命令
Alert anyone to the situation, disobey any of my commands,
试图用任何方式挂断电话
attempt in any way to disconnect this call,
亚伦送命
and Aaron dies.
听着够简单
Sounds simple enough.
很高兴你这么想
I'm glad you think so.
命令一
Command number one:
取消你派去亚伦家的警察
Call off the police you've dispatched to Aaron's home.
马上
Now.
全体注意
All units,
忽略贝克斯菲路216号的非法入室
disregard 1031 at 216 Bakersfield Way.
是恶作剧电话  重复  没有紧急情况
The call was a hoax. Repeat, there is no emergency.
收到  C段取消回应
Copy that. Sector Charlie canceling response.
非常好  桑德拉
Excellent, Sandra.
你会做得很好
You're gonna do just fine.
芬奇  我们进入亚伦的公寓楼了
Finch, we're entering Aaron's apartment building.
什么情况
Any news?
亚伦被人绑架了
Aaron's been abducted by a man
那人能黑进911专用交换分机
who was able to hack into the 911 private branch exchange
让那孩子的电话直接转到桑德拉那里
and ensure that the boy's call went directly to Sandra.
知道为什么非要选中她吗
Any idea why he'd single her out?
可能是因为怀恨在心
Could be a grudge.
桑德拉接过的某个911电话砸了
One of Sandra's 911 calls gone bad.
还是解释不了孩子的事
Doesn't explain the kid, though.
亚伦身陷险境  为什么会跳出桑德拉的号码
Why would Sandra's number come up if Aaron's the one in danger?
既然机器给了我们桑德拉的号码
If the machine gave us Sandra's number,
她和亚伦的命运是联系在一起的
her fate and Aaron's are entwined.
芬奇  没发现他们和孩子
Finch, no sign of them or the kid.
试试网络摄像头
Try the webcam.
我使用了一个远程管理工具
I used a remote administration tool
进入了亚伦的电脑
to access Aaron's computer.
他在这儿
There he is.
抓走他的人很专业
Guys who took him were pros.
不是军人
They're not military.
没清理没确认
No sweep and clear.
中看不中用的镀铬型手枪
Flashy chrome pistol.
那枚戒指  哥特式十字架
And that ring-- a gothic cross.
圣堂武士
Templarios.
绑匪来自墨西哥毒帮
Express kidnappers from a Mexican cartel.
就擅长做这个
Best at what they do.
我定位了神秘来电人的手机GPS信号
I've pinpointed the GPS signal from the mystery caller's phone.
在一辆车上  正在曼哈顿上城转圈
It's in a car cruising upper Manhattan.
我去查
I'm on it.
我去追踪那毒帮
I'll see if I can track down the cartel.
看来那位死掉的姑娘
Looks like your dead girl,
塔拉・库克  在一家私募股权公司工作
Tara Cooke, worked at a private equity firm.
我们去查查她办公室
Let's go check out her office.
我们会进行常规检测
We'll run the usual tests.
不过第一印象  地毯纤维不匹配
But first glance? Carpet fibers aren't a match.
那姑娘不是在办公室被杀的
Your girl wasn't killed in her office.
眼镜儿没跟你说么
Didn't Glasses give you the message?
哥佳人有约了  排队等着去
My dance card's booked.
我在帮个菜鸟查凶杀案
I'm helping a rookie with a homicide.
所以除非是世界末日
So unless the world's coming to an end--
十岁小男孩的世界末日  就靠我们救了
For a ten-year-old boy it is, unless we save him.
怎么不早说  你需要什么
Why didn't you say so? What do you need?
圣堂武士
The Templarios.
知道他们最近在哪里活动吗
Any idea where they've been hanging out lately?
我不太确定
I can't say for sure.
他们通常会在贝德福德公园边的驯鹰酒吧混
They used to frequent a bar up in Bedford Park called El Cetrero.
要我就去那里找  祝你好运
That's where I'd try. Good luck.
你是哪位
And you are?
布伦特・霍尔姆
Brent Holm.
我跟塔拉共事两年了
I worked side by side with Tara for two years.
我听说她是被打劫了
I heard she was mugged.
为什么要检查她的办公室
Why are you checking her office?
只是得排查下
Just have to rule some things out.
我们会提供警方所需的任何资料
We'll provide the police with whatever you need.
你很了解塔拉吗
Did you know Tara as well?
希望是的  我雇了她
I should hope so. I hired her.
吉娜・金凯德  首席财务官
Gina Kincaid, CFO.
这是我丈夫  首席执行官罗恩・金凯德
And this is my husband and CEO Ron Kincaid.
很高兴认识二位
Good to meet you both.
塔拉是优秀的青年主管
Tara was one of our top young executives.
我们会竭尽所能提供帮助
We intend to help in any way we can.
您要真想帮忙吗
You know what would be really helpful?
请给我们一份塔拉最后上班
If you could get us a copy of the security footage
那天的监控录像
of Tara's last day at work.
好了
It's done.
我已经把亚伦的电话标记为恶作剧了
I've labeled Aaron's call a prank.
很好
Good.
现在把耳机插进手机里
Now plug your headset into your phone.
你的双手得解放出来
Your hands need to be free.
做什么
To do what?
关掉大楼的备用发电机
Shut down the building's backup generator.
如果停电的话
If the power goes out,
就只有那组发电机能保持呼叫中心的运转
that generator is the only thing keeping this call center online.
为什么要关掉
Why shut it down?
因为我诚意请求
Because I asked nicely.
我可以来硬的
I can be more emphatic,
但那样就有人要受伤了
but people tend to get hurt when that happens.
好姑娘
Good girl.
别显得那么紧张  桑德拉
And try not to look so nervous, Sandra.
我能看见你的手发抖  那别人也能
If I can see your hands shaking, everyone can.
是在华盛顿高地吗
Is that in Washington Heights?
您说他多大年纪
How old would you say he was?
尽快拿到
Go get them as fast as you can.
您服药多久了
Now how long ago did you take the pills?
您家里有灭火器吗
Do you have a fire extinguisher in the house?
那男人穿的什么
What was the man wearing?
好的  先生  您的位置在哪里
All right, sir. What's your location?
公寓号码是多少
What's the apartment number?
您得尽快离开那里
Then you need to get out of there as quickly as possible.
您的猫卡在空调管里多久了
And how long has your cat been stuck in the A.C. duct?
别试图抢救任何财物  明白吗
Do not attempt to save any of your possessions, okay?
您喝酒了吗
And have you had any alcohol?
其他乘客如何
What about the other passengers?
撞车时有人受伤吗
Anyone hurt when the car hit you?
有没有看见他往哪里跑
Did you see which way he ran--
桑德拉
Sandra...
我想再次感谢你的帮助
I just wanted to thank you again for your help.
-你还好吗  -还好  谢谢
- Are you all right? - Fine. Thanks.
他为什么要让她关掉备用发电机呢
Why would he send her to shut down the backup generator?
有什么能帮你的吗  桑德拉
Can I help you, Sandra?
我真是笨手笨脚
I'm such a klutz.
我想我今早把一只耳环掉在后面了
I think I dropped an earring back there this morning.
我能不能进去找找
Is there any way I could go in and take a look?
登记一下
Just sign in.
帮 我
桑德拉  你真以为我看不到吗
Sandra, did you really think I wouldn't see that?
你肯定毫不在乎亚伦
You must not care about Aaron at all.
就像你二十年前毫不在乎小乔瑟夫
Just like you didn't care about little Joseph 20 years ago.
乔瑟夫
Joseph.
只要资源得当
With the right resources,
什么资料都能拿到
you can access anything...
包括被封存的少年犯罪记录
even sealed juvenile records.
问题是
The question is,
同样的错误你要犯两次吗
are you doomed to make the same mistake twice?
下面很吓人啊  是不是
Creepy down here, isn't it?
好了
All right.
找到备用发电机开关
Now find the backup generator switch,
关了它
and shut it off.
干得好  桑德拉
Nicely done, Sandra.
还有最后一个任务
Just one more task to perform.
到服务器机房
Let's go to the server room.
坐下  登陆
Now have a seat and sign in.
现在
Now...
调出两天前所有接入的911电话
pull up all the 911 calls that came in two days ago.
30918起紧急事件
30,918 emergencies.
纽约啊纽约  真是神奇的城市
New York, New York. It's a wonderful town.
好了  再有一步  亚伦就可以回家了
Okay, one more step, and Aaron is home free.
说吧  赶紧结束吧
Tell me, so we can get this over with.
我要你删了它们  桑德拉  全部
I want you to delete them, Sandra--all of them.
我做不到
I can't.
这些电话是公共记录的一部分
Those calls are part of the public record.
是证据  招供  遗言
They're evidence, confessions, dying words.
不行
I won't.
我已经把要求告诉你了
I've told you what I require.
现在你得做选择了
Now you have to choose.
拯救三万条电话记录  还是一个孩子的生命
Save 30,000 phone calls or the life of one boy.
肖女士  希望你快找到那位神秘来电人了
Ms. Shaw, I do hope you're closing in on our mystery caller
他实在难以捉摸
because he's proving to be quite elusive.
没有证据显示他黑进了摄像头
There's no evidence that he's broken into the camera feeds,
但是他竟然能监视桑德拉的一举一动
yet he's somehow able to watch Sandra's every move.
感谢你发给我的GPS坐标
Thanks to the GPS coordinates you sent me,
我看到他的车了
I've got eyes on his car.
马上  我就看到他了
And in a minute... I'll have eyes on him.
肖女士  你找到来电人了吗
Ms. Shaw, did you find the caller?
芬奇
Finch...
我们有麻烦了
We have a problem.
这家伙不只是个声音  简直是个鬼魂
This guy's not just a voice, he's a ghost.
芬奇  我手里拿的是什么
Finch, you wanna tell me what I'm holding here?
就描述看来  像是电话转接
From the description, it sounds like a phone relay.
来电人的声音从一台电话发出
The caller's voice is carried from one phone,
传到另一台上  最后到桑德拉那里
through the other, and on to Sandra.
他的电话可能来自本市甚至全世界的任何地方
His call could be originating from anywhere in the city or the world.
需要我拆开吗
Should I untape them?
或许你就能追踪这通电话了
Maybe then you can trace the call.
不  肖女士  拜托
No, Ms. Shaw, please.
如果我们拆开手机  通话就断了
If we untether the phones, the call will disconnect,
亚伦也许会被杀
and Aaron may well be killed.
你能从司机身上搜集到什么信息吗
Were you able to glean anything from the driver?
有人付给他一千美元
Some guy paid him 1,000 bucks to
让他带着那手机转一天
drive around all day with the phones in the back,
不知道名字
never got a name.
如果我能查出
If only I could determine
他如何监视桑德拉的就好了
how he's able to keep such a close eye on Sandra.
有多少人  他们俩都有枪吗
How many men were there? Did they both have guns?
女士  您所在处安全吗
Ma'am, are you someplace safe?
那狗有试图咬你吗
Did the dog try to bite you?
我明白了  门锁了吗
I understand. Is the door locked?
我不是说
And I'm not saying--
当然了
Of course.
肖女士  我要去处理一个紧急情况
Ms. Shaw, I have a pressing matter to attend to.
你能否问出付钱给司机的人有何体貌特征
Can you get a description of the man who paid the driver?
乐意效劳
My pleasure.
就当是交换吧  桑德拉
Think of it as an exchange, Sandra.
你删除一天的电话记录
You delete a day's worth of calls,
我让亚伦毫发无伤地回家
and I send Aaron home, happy and intact.
删除它们对你能有什么好处
What good could deleting them possibly do anyone?
简单的解决办法
It's the simpler solution.
既然你有那么多资源  为什么不自己删
Then why not just do it yourself if you have all these resources?
你跟我一样清楚
You know as well as I do
只有你眼前的终端机
that the terminal you're sitting at
才有这一权限
is the only way to access them,
就是说我需要个内部人士  你
which means I need someone on the inside--you.
说够了  要怎么选  桑德拉
Now enough talk. What's it gonna be, Sandra,
电话记录  还是孩子
The calls or the kid?
别转身
Don't turn around.
我远程激活了你手机上的静音键
I have remotely activated the mute function on your cell phone,
所以他听不到我们
so he can't hear us.
那人把一个微型摄像头装在了
Whoever's doing this to you has mounted a tiny webcam
你的耳机上
on your headset.
所以他随时可以监视你
That's how he's been able to watch you
你走到哪里都一样
no matter where you go.
哈罗德
Harold.
-你怎么知道的  -没时间解释了
- How do you know about this? - No time to explain.
你要相信我
You have to trust me.
我有团队在救亚伦
I have a team working to save Aaron,
但我们得查出是谁在幕后操纵
but we need to determine who's behind all of this
以及目的何在
and what he wants.
既然删除三万条电话记录是"简单的解决办法"
If deleting 30,000 calls is the simpler solution,
那么这很可能只是烟雾弹
then that's likely just a smokescreen to
目的是为了删除那个人真正在乎的那通电话
hide the one call that our friend is truly concerned about.
只要我们能找出那通电话
If we could locate that call,
或许可以扭转局势
we might be able to turn the tables on him.
我快失去耐心了  桑德拉
I'm losing patience, Sandra.
我不能一次删除  我得分批删
I can't just hit delete once. I have to do it in batches.
删除一整天的需要十五分钟
It could take 15 minutes for an entire day,
要完成这个  还需要高级管理员密码
and to do that, I need an elite admin code.
只有在信息技术部主管的密钥卡上
Only the head of I.T. has it on a key fob that--
那就别浪费时间了  去找密码
Then stop wasting time, and go get that code!
你去找密码  我待在这儿查电话来源
While you do that, I'll stay here and find that call.
记住  别让我进入你的视线范围内
And remember, keep me out of your line of sight.
我查了塔拉・库克最后上班那天的监控录像
So I checked the security footage from Tara Cooke's last day at work.
早上到  晚上走
Arrives in the morning and leaves at night.
没什么特别的
Nothing unusual.
我只能做出这个
Best I came up with was this--
一份地图  包含塔拉常去的地点
a map of places Tara spent most of her time.
取证时在这些地方都找到了地毯纤维
Forensics got carpet fibers from all these spots.
没有匹配
No matches.
她的同事呢  那位"备加关心"先生
What about that coworker of hers -- Mr. Concerned?
这就去查
I'll check him out.
神奇小子说你们在救个孩子
Wonder Boy tells me you guys are trying to help a kid.
的确如此  警探  我需要你的帮助
Indeed, Detective, which is why I need your help.
我在大海捞针
I'm looking for a needle in a haystack--
从三万通911报警电话里找出一个可疑的
one suspicious 911 call out of 30,000.
三万通
30,000?
那可不是海  那是整个五大洋了
That's not a haystack. That's a whole damn farm.
我已经用概率缩减了总量
Using probabilities, I was able to reduce that number.
比如说  38%打入911报警系统的电话
For instance, 38% of all calls to the 911 system
都是无意按到键盘
are the result of unintended pressure to the keypad.
等等
Wait a minute.
你是说911每天要接到一万一千通误拔电话
You're telling that 911 gets over 11,000 butt dials a day?
恐怕正是如此  但这可以帮我
I'm afraid so, but it did allow me
剔除将近一半的来电
to weed out almost half of the calls.
我同样排除了抢钱包的  车子抛锚的
I also removed purse-snatchings, stalled cars--
你就直说了吧  还有多少电话
Let's cut to the chase. How many calls we gonna look at?
312通  五分钟内找到
312 in the next five minutes.
我把你的那半清单发给你
I'm sending you your half of the list.
附件囊括音频文件
The attachment contains audio files,
连同每个电话号码  通话记录
along with each phone's number, call history,
还有所在位置的地图
and the map of its location data.
五分钟内查找156通来电
156 calls in five minutes?
尽情享受吧  警探
Happy hunting, Detective.
不  应该是10.6版本  好吗
No, it's gotta be version 10.6, okay?
不  我告诉过你
No, I told you.
如果协议不匹配  路由器无法工作
If the protocols don't match, the router won't work.
再试一次
Try again.
托德  你有空吗
Todd, you got a minute?
有一名实习生  猛一拉监控电缆
One of my trainees yanked too hard on a monitor cable,
把接头扯下来了
tore the connector right off.
你有备用的吗
You have a spare?
他们什么时候才能学会尊重科技
When will they learn to respect the tech?
帮我盯一下
Keep an eye on that one.
去取密钥卡
Now get that key fob.
最好快点
Better hurry,
否则会被抓现行
or you're gonna get caught.
给你
Here you go.
谢了
Thanks.
你没事吧  桑德拉
You okay, Sandra?
烦心的电话
Rough call.
时间有限  警探
Time is running out, Detective.
找到那通911报警电话就通知我
Let me know if you find that 911 call.
他每天都偷我的东西
He's stealing from me every day!
那是我的报纸
It's my newspaper!
屋里所有东西都被砸坏了
Breaking everything in the house.
[NBA]尼克斯队一输球就这样
This is how it gets whenever the Knicks lose,
我受够了
and I've had it.
911报警电话  有什么紧急情况
911. What's your emergency?
都怪我  我错了
It's my fault. I was wrong.
我不该和他上床
I shouldn't have slept with him.
他打我
Now he hurt me.
亲  你在哪里
Honey, where are you?
我看到你的电话在25号高速公路向西移动
I see your phone moving west on Highway 25.
我们  我们在开车
We -- we were driving.
我说我要离开他  他  他就打我
I said I was leaving him. He -- he hurt me.
好的  我叫警察去找你
Okay, I've got police coming to find you.
别挂电话
Just stay with me.
你用的预付费手机  我看不到你的名字
You're on a prepaid cell, so I can't see your name.
能告诉我你的名字吗
Wanna tell me your name?
喂  你还在吗  回答我
Hello? Are you there? Answer me.
请回答我
Please answer me.
等等
Wait a minute.
这个来电者的地址和
This caller's phone has been in the same locations
那个菜鸟的谋杀案死者一致
as the rookie's homicide victim.
塔拉
Tara.
眼镜儿  我找到来电了
Glasses, I think I found the call.
如果没错的话  我们查的是同一个案子
And if I'm right, we're working the same case.
纽约驾照
塔拉・库克
谋杀案死者  她用一次性手机打的
Homicide victim. She called from a burner phone.
警察定位到她之前  手机断电了
Battery went dead before police could locate her.
不过我知道她的名字
But I'm pretty sure I know her name.
我现在就把资料发给你
I'm sending you the info now.
新信息
弗斯科
-塔拉・库克  -没错
- Tara Cooke. - Yeah.
我敢说威胁那孩子的人
I'm betting whoever's threatening that kid
就是杀害塔拉的凶手
is the same person who killed Tara.
你有办法能进入塔拉的语音信箱吗
Now is there any way you can access Tara's voice mail?
我试试  警探
I'll try, Detective.
那是谁
Who is that?
谁在帮你
Who is helping you?
没人  我发誓我不认识他
Nobody. I swear I don't know that person.
我可不喜欢听谎言  桑德拉
I'm not a fan of lies, Sandra.
-你违规了  -求你别伤害亚伦
- You broke one of my rules. - Please don't hurt Aaron.
你早想到亚伦
You should've thought of Aaron
就不该把其他人牵扯进来
before you involved someone else in our arrangement.
现在我别无选择
Now I have no choice.
我说话算话
I'm a man of my word.
记住  这都怪你
Just remember, this was your fault.
911报警电话  有什么紧急情况
911. What is your emergency?
要我叫辆救护车过去吗
Would you like me to send an ambulance to your location?
爆炸  您确定吗
An explosion. Are you sure?
爆炸地点在哪里  先生
Where was the bomb when it went off, sir?
-您还好吗  是否有人受伤  -明白  先生
- Are you all right? Is anyone injured? - I understand, sir.
爆炸大概震碎了多少窗户
How many windows were shattered from the explosion?
据您所见  是否有人受伤
And as far as you can tell, was anyone injured?
他死了吗  你杀了亚伦吗
Is he dead? Did you kill Aaron?
我引爆的地点是一个车库
The bomb I exploded was in a parking garage.
三辆车已经烧成了废铁
Three cars were turned into flaming metal husks.
就当这是鸣枪示警吧
Call it a warning shot.
亚伦还活着  暂时
Aaron is still alive... for the moment.
好  我明白
Okay, I understand.
不  我想你不明白
No, I don't think you do.
同样大小的炸弹
You see, a bomb of the exact same size
正绑在小亚伦的身上
is currently strapped to little Aaron.
鉴于我的规则对你来说太过复杂
And since my rules have proven too complicated for you to follow,
下面我就简单来
I'm gonna make this all very simple.
给你十五分钟时间删除来电
You have exactly 15 minutes to delete those calls
否则我就引爆炸弹  计时开始
before I set that bomb off, starting now.
动手吧
Do it!
否则你下一个出警电话
Or the next dispatch call you make
就是安排警员们去收拾
will be to have officers pick up the pieces
那小男孩的残肢了
of what's left of that boy's body.
你现在明白了吗  桑德拉
Do you understand me now, Sandra?
一开始看来  这根本没道理
At first, it didn't make sense.
同一楼层有那么多接线员
Of all the operators out there on that floor,
为什么偏偏选了一个看似最坚强的
why pick the one who is least likely to crack under pressure
最不可能乖乖听话的
and give in to his demands?
这是蠢招
A foolish move...
除非他了解你的某件事
unless he knew something about you...
某件封存在少年犯罪记录中的事
something in a sealed juvenile record
他可以凭此作为完美的筹码
that he could twist into the perfect leverage
要挟你听他的话
to get you to do what he was asking.
孩子死亡
The loss of a child.
他叫乔瑟夫
His name was Joseph.
那年他三岁
He was three years old,
他的笑容灿烂得能点亮世界
and he had a smile that just made everything okay.
我住在他对街
I lived across the street,
经常去当他的保姆
used to babysit him all the time.
我十四岁那年的一个晚上  正在给他洗澡
And one night, when I was 14, I was giving him a bath.
他想要玩具
He wanted a toy.
一只可笑的黄色青蛙
Ridiculous yellow frog.
放在楼下
It was just downstairs.
我只走开了一分钟  但是
I was only gone a minute, but...
之后你大概能猜到了
You can probably guess the rest.
最痛苦的  不是我拼命给他做心脏复苏
The worst part wasn't... desperately trying to perform CPR
盼着医护人员快来
before the paramedics arrived
甚至不是警方指控我过失杀人
or even when the police charged me with negligent homicide.
最痛苦的
No, the worst part...
是我回到楼上
was when I came back upstairs
看见他面朝下倒在浴缸中
and I found him lying facedown in the tub.
我僵住了
I froze.
我没法思考  也没法动弹
I couldn't think. I couldn't move.
直到今天  我都在想也许那僵住的十五秒
And to this day, I wonder whether those extra 15 seconds
能救回乔瑟夫的生命
wouldn't have saved Joseph's life.
你当时也只是孩子
You were just a child yourself.
任何人在那种情况下
Anyone in those circumstances--
我的律师当时也是那么说的
That's what my lawyer said.
在法律角度看来
And in the eyes of the law,
我是无辜的
I was found innocent.
但在我看来不是的  哈罗德
But not in my eyes, Harold.
所以我会照那个人说的做
Which is why I'm gonna do whatever this man wants.
桑德拉  等等
Sandra, wait.
他会找上你还有第二个原因
There's a second reason why the caller is targeting you--
你两天前接到的一通911报警电话  一起谋杀案
a 911 call you took two days ago, a murder.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我不会再放弃一个孩子
I'm not giving up on another little boy.
我会尽量争取时间
I'll give you as many minutes as I can,
然后我会删除记录
and then I'm deleting those calls.
我现在要转身了  请你让开
I'm turning around now. Please get out of my way.
我明白  你不会放弃亚伦
I understand you won't give up on Aaron.
我也不会放弃你
I won't give up on you.
肖女士  如果那两台捆绑电话还在你手上
Ms. Shaw, if you still have those tethered phones,
拿好
hold on to them.
我有事要做
I have work to do.
问出体貌特征了
Got a description.
可能是我们要找的人
Might be the guy we're looking for.
好  肖  说来听听
All right, Shaw, let's hear it.
拉丁裔  西装笔挺
Latino in a slick suit.
右耳上的耳钉多到抽疯
Ridiculous number of piercings in his right ear,
包括一个哥特式十字架
including a gothic cross.
圣堂武士
Templario.
我怎么一点也不惊讶呢
Why am I not surprised?
驯鹰酒吧
看到了
There he is.
五个的确有点抽疯
Five does seem a bit ridiculous.
我现在赶过去  你不必独自上阵
I'm on way. No need to handle this on your own.
等支援向来不是咱的范儿
Never been one to wait for backup.
只想跟他略谈句
Just want a quick conversation with him.
其他人可以退下了
The rest of you can...leave.
免得受伤
Nobody gets hurt.
免得受伤  那你呢  [西语]蠢货
Nobody gets hurt? How about you, pendejo?
爷就盼着你们敬酒不吃吃罚酒
I was kinda hoping you'd pick the hard way.
眼镜儿  我发现了点情况
Glasses, got some interesting information
谋杀案死者和她的老板金凯德夫妇之间有点问题
about my homicide victim and her bosses, the Kincaids.
也许能帮上那个小孩儿
Might help you with your kid.
这边搞定就打给你
Call you when I'm done.
我只剩一个问题了
I just got one other question.
知道塔拉手里的是什么吗
Any idea what Tara has in her hand?
她的手机
That's her cell phone.
这才是她的手机
在她公寓发现的
Found in her apartment.
这是一次性手机
That is a burner phone.
塔拉死的那晚在她身上
Tara had it on her the night she died,
但在她的物品中死活找不到
but can't seem to find it in any of her things.
看来是有人处理掉了
Turns out somebody got rid of it...
杀害她的那个人
Somebody who killed her.
我们调取了通话记录
We accessed the phone records.
塔拉只用这个手机打给过两个号码
Tara used that burner phone to only call two numbers--
在她被杀当晚拨打的911  以及
911 the night she died, and...
这个号码  见过吗
this one. Recognize it?
我也没见过
Me neither.
所以我们决定查下这个语音信箱
That's why we decided to check its voice mail.
我知道  没密码怎么查呢  对吧
I know, how do you do that without the code, right?
我有个朋友刚好
I got this friend of mine who's just--
很擅长这些事
he's great at that type of thing.
罗恩  我是塔拉
Ron, it's Tara.
我不能再继续下去  再偷偷摸摸下去
I-I can't do this anymore, the sneaking around.
这样对我和吉娜都不公平
It's not fair to me or to Gina.
我要公开
I wanna tell the world about us.
就算被删的语音留言三十天内也能找回
Even deleted voice mails can be retrieved for up to 30 days.
1和0组合的数据  永远不会彻底消失
Ones and zeros, they never really go away.
这些法庭都不会认可
None of this is admissible in court.
但这个可以
But this is.
这些地毯纤维取自你的后备箱
Carpet fibers from the mat in your trunk,
就是罗恩打死她之后装她尸体的地方
which is where Ron stuffed the body after he hit her...
然后他把她抛尸河中了
before he dumped her down by the river.
但最让你恐惧的是发现她打了911报警电话
But the real scare came when you realized she made a 911 call.
你不知道她电话里说了什么
You didn't know what was on that call,
但你知道你必须处理掉
but you knew you needed to get rid of it.
要是平常  我容你矢口否认
See, normally, I'd let you squirm and deny it.
但你居然绑架孩子来掩盖罪行
But you had to kidnap a little boy to cover it up.
孩子  什么
Little boy. What?
现在你给我拿起电话
Now you're gonna get on that phone,
给我告诉他们放了他
and you're gonna tell 'em to let him go.
等等  他只是要处理那通电话记录
Wait. He was just supposed to get rid of the call.
-没说任何关于  -谁
- He never said anything about... - Who?
你雇了谁
Who'd you hire?
我不知道
I don't know.
罗恩告诉我他干了什么
Ron told me what he'd done.
我就找了专门处理这些事的人
I found someone who could get rid of the problem.
如何叫停
How do you call it off?
我没问过
I never asked.
别担心  肖
Don't worry, Shaw.
我把好戏留在最后了
I saved the best for last.
就是你吗
Are you him...
是你恐吓911接线员
the guy who's been terrorizing a 911 operator
威胁要炸死小孩吗
and threatening to blow up a kid?
[西语]别做梦了  小妞
Ni madres, mija.
你抓不到他的
You'll never catch him.
那家伙很小心
Guy's careful.
电话无法追查  短信自我删除
Untraceable calls, self-deleting texts.
我们照他说的办事  钱就能到账
We do what he asks, the money shows up in an account.
好吧  我就简单直接点
Yeah, I'm gonna make this simple.
说  孩子关哪儿了
You're gonna tell us where you're holding the boy.
没门
No way.
[西语]打死我也不说
Soy una tumba.
你就开枪吧
You're going to have to shoot me.
那个嘛
That...
就没必要了
won't be necessary.
马上到  先生
On their way, sir.
请你保持通话
I just need you to stay on the phone with me.
里瑟先生  肖女士  我有消息了
Mr. Reese, Ms. Shaw, I have news.
我黑进了肖女士找到的
I was able to hack into the one cell phone tower
那两台捆绑电话的转接手机信号发射塔
relaying signals from both the tethered phones Ms. Shaw found.
我知道神秘人是从哪儿打过来的了
I know where our mystery man is calling from.
很有可能就在他们关亚伦的地方
Chances are it's the same place they're holding Aaron--
中城区的一栋办公楼
An office tower in midtown.
已经到了  芬奇
Already there, Finch.
圣堂武士供出亚伦的位置了吗
The Templario gave up Aaron's location?
想办法撬出来了
We managed to pry it out of him.
千万小心
Please be careful.
此人智商极高
The man we're looking for is highly intelligent,
神通广大  逼急了不择手段
resourceful, and no doubt dangerous when cornered.
简而言之  芬奇  他就是你
So basically, Finch, he's you...
你的邪恶版
if you were evil.
鄙人不甚欣赏如此类比  肖女士
I hardly welcome the comparison, Ms. Shaw.
抓紧时间
Please hurry.
此人绑架小孩来帮助杀人犯
This man kidnapped a child to help a killer,
如果桑德拉真的删了那些通话记录他就成功了
and he'll succeed if Sandra deletes those calls.
干嘛  要新西服啊
What, you need a new suit?
输入密码
准许进入
删除
确定删除数据?
停
Stop.
我刚发现
I've just been informed
雇我的客户
that the clients who hired me for this job
向警方自首了
have confessed to the police.
既然如此  我和他们的合同现在无效了
As such, my contract with them is now null and void.
我不再需要你的服务了  桑德拉
Your services in this matter are no longer required, Sandra.
那结束了  你放亚伦走
So it's over. You're letting Aaron go.
很不幸  现在不可能了
Regretfully, that has now become impossible.
我不能冒险将这次行动细节
I simply cannot risk any details of this operation
曝露给警方
falling into police hands.
要干净利落
Cleanliness is all.
别怪自己  你尽力了
Don't blame yourself. You did everything you could.
别这样  我求你了
Don't do this, I'm begging you.
抱歉  桑德拉  对亚伦来说太晚了
I'm sorry, Sandra. It's too late for Aaron.
你也一样
and for you as well.
当然了  除掉你
Though, of course, eliminating you
一直是计划的一部分
was always part of the plan.
与你通话很愉快  桑德拉
It was a genuine pleasure speaking with you, Sandra.
拜
Good-bye.
桑德拉
Sandra.
-别去  -这是规定
- Don't. - It's protocol.
停电时
During a blackout,
我们都要从前门撤离
we're all supposed to exit through the front.
那就正中来电人的下怀了
Which is exactly what the man who called you will be waiting for.
有别的出口吗
Is there another way out?
跟我来
Follow me.
[西语]我们走  撤
Vamonos. Let's go.
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
电梯应该早停了
I thought the elevator was locked.
我们得拆除炸弹
We gotta defuse that bomb.
团队里不允许死亡
There is no "dead" in "team."
别跟我玩儿孤胆英雄那套
So instead of going all Charles Bronson on me,
动作巨星  七十年代"全球最受欢迎的艺人"
我先清理出路
let me clear that way.
你是亚伦  是吗
You're Aaron, right?
我是来帮你的
I'm here to help.
那里有个出口
There's an exit down there.
桑德拉
Sandra!
水平开关  别动
A level switch. Hold very still.
亚伦
Aaron.
你喜欢棒球  是吧
You like baseball, right?
是  但是我击打不好
Yeah, but I'm not a very good hitter.
我以前也这样
I used to have the same problem.
知道如何改进吗
Know what helped?
每天晚上  我闭上眼
Every night, I'd close my eyes...
想象我打出了本垒打
imagine myself hitting one out of the park.
我发现关键在于时机
I realized it was all about timing.
想试试吗
Wanna give it a try?
试试吧
Go ahead.
看见球过来了吗  亚伦
See that pitch coming, Aaron?
看见了
Yeah.
全力挥棒
Swing as hard as you can.
动手
Now.
我成功了
I did it.
是的  你成功了
Yeah, you did.
最后一名绑架犯搞定
Got the last kidnapper.
知道谁是幕后主使了吗
You figure out which one was behind all this?
是的
Yeah.
谁都不是
None of them.
他还逍遥在外
Then he's still out there.
别动
Don't move.
别急着妄动送命
Before you make a grave error of judgment,
请允许我先描述一下我手里的东西
permit me to describe what I have in my hand.
是一根切断的电线  连在了发电机上
It's a severed electrical cable connected to this generator.
电线里的电流
Current is running through it
是电刑所需的十倍
at ten times the amperage required for electrocution.
我只需要把它扔在水里
All I have to do is drop it in that water,
三秒之后
and within three seconds,
你心脏上的肌肉就会开始纤维性颤动
the muscles in your heart will fibrillate.
鄙人向来不尚暴力
Now I'm not a violent man.
但你不仅想要伤害这位女士
But not only have you tried to harm this young woman
和一名无辜儿童
and an innocent child,
还关闭了全世界
you have shut down a 911 call center
最危险城市的911报警中心
in one of the more dangerous cities in the country.
现在只有乖乖做两件事
So now there are two things that will keep me
可以保住你的命
from ending your life right now.
第一  我要你扔掉枪
First, I want you to drop the gun.
第二  我要听到你的声音
Second, I need to hear the sound of your voice.
拜托  我只是受雇于人
Please. I just work for the guy.
我甚至不知道他的名字
I don't even know his name.
桑德拉  拿走他的武器
Sandra, get his weapon.
想再次谢谢你的帮助
Just wanted to say thanks again for all your help.
金凯德夫妇请了律师
The Kincaids have lawyered up.
不过罗恩后备箱里的地毯纤维
But the carpet fibers in Ron's trunk
和塔拉尸体上发现的相匹配
are a match for the ones found on Tara's body.
再加上电话记录
So between that and the phone records,
定罪应该不成问题
shouldn't be too hard to get a conviction.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
同喜
Yeah, you too.
我觉得  我们是很棒的团队
I'd say we make a pretty good team.
你不觉得吗
Don't you think?
我们才不是团队
We ain't a team.
干嘛  你就准备傻站在那儿吗
What, are you gonna stand there all day?
灌杯咖啡  继续工作去
Get yourself a cup of coffee and get back to work.
我又不能帮你解决全部案子
I can't help you solve all your cases.
-桑德拉  -哈罗德
- Sandra. - Harold.
很高兴你可以来见我
So glad you could meet.
我正要去上班  这点事还能做到
I was on my way to work. It's the least I could do.
我欠你一条命
I owe you my life.
我很高兴可以帮到你
I was happy to lend a hand.
坦白说
To tell you the truth,
我觉得我们志趣相投
I've come to think of us as kindred spirits,
接到紧急电话  帮助需要帮助的人
Taking emergency calls to help those who need us.
你是这样找到我的吗
So is that how you found me?
接到了电话
You got a call?
差不多吧
Something like that.
我想说的是
What I mean to say is...
我很欣慰这个世界上有你们的存在
It does my heart good to know that you're out there.
彼此彼此  哈罗德  我该去工作了
Likewise, Harold. I should get to work.
离开之前  那里
Before you leave, there was...
我想给你看下
something I'd like to show you.
打得不错  亚伦
Nice hit, Aaron.
是他吗
Is that him?
我想让你享受一下
I wanted to offer you the one thing
911接线员永远得不到的东西  了结
that 911 operators never get--closure.
亚伦看起来很开心
Aaron looks happy.
看不到他经历过什么
You'd never guess what he'd been through.
孩子的恢复能力很强
Kids are resilient creatures.
大人其实也是如此  只要有对的朋友
As are adults, if they have the right friends.
感谢两位出色地完成了任务
My deepest thanks to both of you for a job well done.
没有全部完成
Not quite done.
如果你还想找到那个人
If you still wanna find the guy,
这个也许有用
maybe these could help.
电话打进
未知号码
喂
Hello?
终于
Finally.
跟让我首场败绩的人对话
A chance to speak to the man who handed me my first defeat.
我不是一个人
I didn't do it alone.
相信我  我非常清楚
Believe me, I'm quite aware.
我警告你
I'm warning you now,
如果你再想伤害桑德拉或者亚伦
any attempt to harm either Sandra or Aaron again
你会后悔
would be a mistake.
不用担心
No need to worry.
在我看来  桑德拉小命得保了
Sandra's earned her life, as far as I'm concerned.
此时此刻
And at this point,
伤害亚伦已经毫无意义了
harming Aaron would be counterproductive.
而你  则完全不同
You, however, are another story entirely.
后会有期
Be seeing you.
他说什么了
What did he say?
无足轻重
Nothing of any consequence.